You are using AlgoKit version 2.7.1, however version 2.10.2 is available. Please update using the tool used to install AlgoKit.
Usage: algokit init [OPTIONS] COMMAND [ARGS]...

  Initializes a new project from a template, including prompting for template
  specific questions to be used in template rendering.

  Templates can be default templates shipped with AlgoKit, or custom templates
  in public Git repositories.

  Includes ability to initialise Git repository, run algokit project bootstrap
  and automatically open Visual Studio Code.

  This should be run in the parent directory that you want the project folder
  created in.

  By default, the `--workspace` flag creates projects within a workspace
  structure or integrates them into an existing one, promoting organized
  management of multiple projects. Alternatively, to disable this behavior use
  the `--no-workspace` flag, which ensures the new project is created in a
  standalone target directory. This is suitable for isolated projects or when
  workspace integration is unnecessary.

Options:
  -n, --name TEXT                 Name of the project / directory / repository
                                  to create.
  -t, --template [tealscript|typescript|python|react|fullstack|base]
                                  Name of an official template to use. To
                                  choose interactively, run this command with
                                  no arguments.
  --template-url URL              URL to a git repo with a custom project
                                  template.
  --template-url-ref URL          Specific tag, branch or commit to use on git
                                  repo specified with --template-url. Defaults
                                  to latest.
  --UNSAFE-SECURITY-accept-template-url
                                  Accept the specified template URL,
                                  acknowledging the security implications of
                                  arbitrary code execution trusting an
                                  unofficial template.
  --git / --no-git                Initialise git repository in directory after
                                  creation.
  --defaults                      Automatically choose default answers without
                                  asking when creating this template.
  --bootstrap / --no-bootstrap    Whether to run `algokit project bootstrap`
                                  to install and configure the new project's
                                  dependencies locally.
  --ide / --no-ide                Whether to open an IDE for you if the IDE
                                  and IDE config are detected. Supported IDEs:
                                  VS Code.
  --workspace / --no-workspace    Whether to prefer structuring standalone
                                  projects as part of a workspace. An AlgoKit
                                  workspace is a conventional project
                                  structure that allows managing multiple
                                  standalone projects in a monorepo.
  -a, --answer <key> <value>      Answers key/value pairs to pass to the
                                  template.
  -h, --help                      Show this message and exit.

Commands:
  example  Initialize a new project from an example template.
